Collection of Bookplates by J. Winfred Spenceley
Yale University Arts Library
- Other Works, Series IV
  - Various Decorative & Commercial Decorative, undated; 36 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    Includes various states of mostly decorative illustrations. Also includes original drawings by Spenceley for printing ornaments and initial capitals on a galley proof folio from Voyage autor de ma chambre.
- Correspondence and Ephemera, Series V
  This series includes a variety of correspondence and ephemera either by or about Spenceley, such as exhibition announcements, business announcements, correspondence regarding bookplate commissions, later correspondence regarding the collecting of Spenceley works, as well as original sketches and tracings by the artist.
  - Various Correspondence and Lists, Notations & Postcards, etc. Also Sketches, Tracings, etc., 1905-1937 undated; 22 (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Additional Correspondence and Ephemera by or about Spenceley, 1899-1933 undated; 2 (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Notes on Series I, III, IV, and V, undated; 20 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    Includes handwritten lists which identify and describe some of the materials in Series I, III, IV, and V of this collection.